art21.org 2019-05-01

# Privacy Policy | Art21

Art21, Inc. (herein known as “Art21”) values the privacy of the users of the Art21 website, located at art21.org (herein known as “Art21 Site”). Art21 does not collect personal information about you—such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address—unless you voluntarily and knowingly provide it.

When you register to use certain areas on the Art21 Site, we do request that you provide personal information. The information you provide may be shared among internal staff at Art21. The information will not be shared with any other third parties.

If you provide your email address, it will not be included in Art21’s mailing lists for communication unless stated. Any email you may receive from Art21 will contain instructions directing you how to stop receiving further electronic correspondence from Art21. If you choose to register and provide personal information, you agree to the terms and conditions, applicable to personal information, contained in this Privacy Policy.

Technical information—such as the date, time, and length of your visit; browser type; and IP address—may be collected and used internally for site management purposes. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user, in the event it becomes necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use or to protect the Art21 Site and its users.

Forums and blogs on the Art21 Site may display the name, if provided, of the person posting comments. When providing any personal information on the forums and blogs of the Art21 Site, be aware that you are providing this personal information, that it will be accessible to users of the Art21 Site, and that you are willing to assume the risk and any consequences of providing such information. We cannot guarantee the security and/or privacy of information you choose to disclose online. Remember: whenever you provide personal information online, that information can be collected and used by others.

Art21 does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from children. Visitors to the Art21 Site under the age of 18 are specifically instructed NOT to provide their name, email address, or any personal information on the forums or blogs on the Art21 Site. For younger visitors to the Art21 Site, an adult must provide any personal information on their behalf.

Art21 may place information, known as a “cookie,” on your computer to allow us to identify you, as this information can enable us to better serve you. If you wish to disable the cookies, you may set your browser to do so.

Art21 reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. Should we decide to make such a change, we will conspicuously post such changes, so you will know exactly what information is being collected, how we intend to use the information collected, whether it will be disclosed to anyone, and how you can participate or not (“opt-in” or “opt-out”) in having this information collected.

The Art21 Site provides links to third-party websites. Art21 is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of those linked sites.

Please read the Copyright Notice and Terms of Use notice for the Art21 Site. Use of the Art21 Site is subject to both the Privacy Policy and the Copyright Notice and Terms of Use, which can be accessed via the Terms of Use link in the site-wide footer section of the Art21 Site.

By accessing this Art21 Site, you accept without limitation or qualification the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and the Copyright Notice and Terms of Use.

We encourage your suggestions and input regarding these privacy issues.
